What color would you like to be?
(Leonard:)Well, I'd like to be green,
but you know you always take it.
(Sheldon:)That's not true.
Any color's fine with me.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I could be a-a combination
of blue and yellow.
(Leonard:)Blue and yellow make green.
(Sheldon:)Well, then it's settled.
(Penny:)Hi. Ready to go?
(Sheldon:)Oh, good news, we ordered lunch,
(Sheldon:)so we can all stay here
and play Lord of the Rings Risk.
(Amy:)Sheldon, we said that we would
play games with you tonight.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, we'll still
be playing it tonight--
(Sheldon:)this game can easily
take eight hours.
(Penny:)Sweetie, you really thought
I'd want to do this?
(Leonard:)No.
Well, did you
tell him that?
(Leonard:)Yes.
Did you say it
out loud with words?
(Leonard:)No.
(Penny:)I don't want to spend the whole
day playing a board game.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, you may change
your mind when you hear
(Sheldon:)that this is the
new expanded edition
(Sheldon:)which contains a more
complete map of Middle Earth,
(Sheldon:)now including
the Haradwaith Territories.
(Amy:)I will literally
race you to the car.
(Leonard:)No, no, no, come on,
don't leave. Just try it.